creativetimes.co.uk 2013-05-19

# Privacy Policy | Creative Times

## Privacy Policy

#### Creative Times is committed to protecting your privacy.

The text below describes the ways in which we collect information from you when you use the service, and what we may use it for. Our privacy policy forms part of the terms and conditionsfor use of this website. By agreeing to these terms and conditions, you are consenting to our use of your personal data in accordance with this privacy policy.

Creative Times is a Community Interest Companhy. The registered offices are located at 165E Burton Road, West Didsbury, Manchester, M20 2LN. If you have any other questions about this policy you can write to us at our head office for the attention of Phil Birchenall – or by email to [birchenall@thewhiteroomcec.com](mailto:birchenall@thewhiteroomcec.com)

#### What data do we collect from you?

We collect data from you (‘user data’) when you register to use this website and to receive newsletters, resources and information about events and opportunities.

This data can sometimes comprise personal data about individuals, to which UK data protection laws apply. These terms and conditions and the privacy protection policy describe Creative Times?s approach to fulfilling their obligations under those data protection laws.

#### The information we collect

We may use “cookies” to store certain types of information each time you interact with our website. Cookies enable us to recognise your computer and allow us to see how you use our website. For example, we may track the areas of the website you visit to see what interests you in particular, and which sites you accessed the website from, and leave to visit next. It is normally possible to alter the settings of your computer so that cookies cannot be used in this way, but this may affect the way in which you can use our website. We also note, and save, information such as time of day, browser type and content requested. That information is used to provide more relevant services to our users.

When you register as a user of our website, you will need to provide us with some of your personal data.

#### How we may use this information

Your personal data is stored and processed on computers in the United Kingdom.

We may use your personal data to communicate with you on any matter relating to our website. We may also use your personal data for various administrative functions connected with the website. Otherwise, we will only use your personal data for the purposes for which it was collected, unless you give us or have given us permission to use it for other purposes. (e.g display on the directory section of this website) We will not disclose your personal data to any third party without your permission, other than in the circumstances set out in this privacy policy or where such disclosure is required or permitted by law.

We may collect and analyse data from the personal data provided by you to help us to understand our users as a group so that we can provide a better service. We may share aggregated data with selected third parties, without disclosing individual names or personally identifying information.

From time to time Creative Times may wish to send you information about other services which we offer and believe you may be interested in. We may use user data for this purpose. If you decide now, or at any later time, that you do not wish to receive this information, please inform us by email at info@creativetimes.co.uk

We may change this privacy policy from time to time. Any changes will be displayed on our website. You are deemed to have agreed to any changes when you next use our website following any such change.

We will answer any additional questions you may have. Our e-mail address is: [info@creativetimes.co.uk](mailto:info@creativetimes.co.uk)
